Guide to the CASA Latina Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- EXECUTIVE BOARD [SERIE 2: JUNTA DIRECTIVA], 1996-2015; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 1/67, 3/1-2, 3/4, 3/6-9, 3/12-76, 3/83-115, 4/6-13, 4/47, 4/49-50, 4/59-68, 4/70-72, 4/78, 7/5-7/7, 9/26, 9/37, 9/56, 10/5, 11/42-45, 13/4-6, Reading Room Virtual Vault)
  - Meeting Minutes and Attached Materials [Subserie C: Notas y Documentos de la Junta Directiva], 1995-2015; Subseries C (Box-folder 3/13-15, 3/17-76, 3/83-115, 4/9, 4/13, 4/59-68, 4/70-72, 7/5-7/7, 9/26, 9/37, 9/56, 11/42-45, 13/4-6)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2008 December (Box-folder 3/64)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 January (Box-folder 3/66)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 February (Box-folder 3/67)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 March (Box-folder 3/68)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 April (Box-folder 3/69)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 May (Box-folder 3/70)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 June (Box-folder 3/71)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 July (Box-folder 3/72)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 October (Box-folder 3/73)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 November (Box-folder 3/74)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 December (Box-folder 3/75)
    - CASA Latina Board Decisions [Decisiones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2000-2009 (Box-folder 3/76)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2010 January (Box-folder 3/83)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2010 February (Box-folder 3/84)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2010 March (Box-folder 3/85)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2010 April (Box-folder 3/86)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2010 May (Box-folder 3/87)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2010 June (Box-folder 3/88)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2010 July (Box-folder 3/89)
    - CASA Latina Special Meeting of the Board to Approve 2009 Audited Financial Statement [Reunión Especial de la Junta Directiva para Aprobar Estado Financiero Auditado de 2009], 2010 August (Box-folder 3/90)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2010 September (Box-folder 3/91)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2010 October (Box-folder 3/92)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2010 November (Box-folder 3/93)
    - CASA Latina Annual Meeting of Board and Staff [Reunión Anual de la Junta Directiva y Personal de CASA Latina], 2011 January (Box-folder 3/94)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2011 February (Box-folder 3/95)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2011 March (Box-folder 3/96)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2011 April (Box-folder 3/97)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2001 May (Box-folder 3/98)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2011 June (Box-folder 3/99)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2011 September (Box-folder 3/100)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2011 October (Box-folder 3/101)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2011 November (Box-folder 3/102)
    - CASA Latina Annual Meeting of Board and Staff [Reunión Anual de la Junta Directiva y Personal de CASA Latina], 2012 January (Box-folder 3/103)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 February (Box-folder 3/104)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 March (Box-folder 3/105)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 May (Box-folder 3/106)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 June (Box-folder 3/107)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 July (Box-folder 3/108)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 September (Box-folder 3/109)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 October (Box-folder 3/110)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 November (Box-folder 3/111)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 December (Box-folder 3/112)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 April (Box-folder 3/113)
    - CASA Latina Board Work Plan 2012-2013 [Plan de Trabajo de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2012 December 8 (Box-folder 3/114)
    - CASA Latina Board Resolution Authorizing Loan [Resolución de la Junta Directiva para Autorizar Préstamo], 2013 December (Box-folder 3/115)
    - Board of Directors Retreat [Retiro de la Junta Directiva], 1998 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Board Retreat [Retiro de la Junta Directiva], 1999 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1995 November 20 (Box-folder 4/59)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1996 January (Box-folder 4/60)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1996 February (Box-folder 4/61)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1996 April (Box-folder 4/62)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1996 May (Box-folder 4/63)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1996 July (Box-folder 4/64)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1996 August (Box-folder 4/65)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1996 September (Box-folder 4/66)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1996 October (Box-folder 4/67)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1996 November (Box-folder 4/68)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1997 January (Box-folder 4/70)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1997 February (Box-folder 4/71)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reuniones de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 1997 March (Box-folder 4/72)
    - Board/Staff Retreat [Retiro de Junta Directiva/Personal], 2008 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Advisory Board Committee [Comité Consultivo], 2006 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Advisory Board Action [Acción de Comité Consultivo], 2008 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Executive Director (Hilary Stern) Review [Evaluación de Director Ejecutivx (Hilary Stern)], 2007 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Executive Committee and Board Materials [Materiales del Comité Ejecutivx y Junta Directiva], 2008-2009 (Box-folder 9/37)
    - Hilary Stern--Miscellaneous Notes, Receipts, Correspondence [Hilary Stern--Notas Misceláneas, Recibos, Correspondencia] (Box-folder 9/56)
    - Board Minutes--Part 1 of 2 [Actas de la Junta Directiva--Parte 1 de 2], 2006 (Box-folder 11/42)
    - Board Minutes--Part 2 of 2 [Actas de la Junta Directiva--Parte 2 de 2], 2006 (Box-folder 11/43)
    - Board Minutes--Part 1 of 2 [Actas de la Junta Directiva--Parte 1 de 2], 2007 (Box-folder 11/44)
    - Board Minutes--Part 2 of 2 [Actas de la Junta Directiva--Parte 2 de 2], 2007 (Box-folder 11/45)
    - Board Minutes--Part 1 of 3 [Actas de la Junta Directiva--Parte 1 de 3], 2002 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Board Minutes--Part 2 of 3 [Actas de la Junta Directiva--Parte 2 de 3], 2002 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Board Minutes--Part 3 of 3 [Actas de la Junta Directiva--Parte 3 de 3], 2002 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Board Minutes 2000 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2000], 2000 January-2000 September (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2001 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2001], 2001 February-2001 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2002 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2002], 2002 March-2002 November (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2003 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2003], 2003 January-2003 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2004 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2004], 2004 January-2004 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2005 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2005], 2005 January-2005 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2006 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2006], 2006 January-2006 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2007 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2007], 2007 January-2007 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2008 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2008], 2008 January-2008 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2009 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2009], 2009 January-2009 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2010 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2010], 2010 January-2010 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2011 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2011], 2011 January-2011 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2012 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2012], 2012 January-2012 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2013 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2013], 2013 January-2013 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2014 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2014], 2014 January-2014 December (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
    - Board Minutes 2015 [Actas de la Junta Directiva 2015], 2015 January-2015 September (Electronic file Reading Room Virtual Vault)
- REPORTS AND STATISTICS [SERIE 3: REPORTES Y ESTADÍSTICAS], 1995-2009; SERIES 3 (Box-folder 1/68, 3/11, 3/52, 3/80, 4/22, 4/33, 4/45, 4/57, 4/73, 5/44, 5/57, 7/8, 7/36-40, 7/42, 7/47, 7/61-62, 8/39-40, 8/56-58, 9/30, 10/7, 10/21, 10/30, 12/11, 13/7)
  Annual reports, work and business plans, conference notes from CASA Latina and external conferences, and statistics on CASA Latina programs. Related program and statistical data may also be found in SERIES 5: PROGRAM FILES. [Reportes anuales, planes de trabajo y negocio, notas de conferencias de CASA Latina y externas, y estadísticas y datos de programas de CASA Latina. Datos y estadísticas relacionados a programas también se encuentran en SERIE 5: ARCHIVOS DE PROGRAMAS.]
  - Work and Business Plans [Subserie A: Planes para Trabajos y Negocios], 1996-2006; Subseries A (Box-folder 3/11, 4/22, 4/45, 5/44, 7/42, 7/47, 7/61-62, 9/30, 10/7)
    - CASA Latina Strategic Plan [Plan Estratégico CASA Latina], 2000-2004 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Master Business Plan [Plan Maestro de Negocios], 1996 April 12 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Minute from Strategic Planning [Notas de Reunión para Plan Estratégico], 1999 (Box-folder 4/45)
    - CASA Latina Monthly Service Summary [CASA Latina Resumen de Servicio Mensual], 1997 (Box-folder 5/44)
    - CASA Latina Game Plan [Plan de Juego CASA Latina], 2005 March 26-2005 April 8 (Box-folder 7/42)
    - Program Workplans [Plan de Trabajo de Programa], 2001-2002 (Box-folder 7/47)
    - 5-Year Business Plan (1 of 2) [Plan de Negocios de Cinco Años (1 de 2)], 2005 (Box-folder 7/61)
    - 5-Year Business Plan (2 of 2) [Plan de Negocios de Cinco Años (2 de 2)], 2005 (Box-folder 7/62)
    - 5-Year Business Plan [Plan de Negocios de Cinco Años], 2005 (Box-folder 9/30)
    - 5-Year Business Plan [Plan de Negocios de Cinco Años], 2006 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Annual Reports [Subserie B: Reportes Anuales], 1995-2005; Subseries B (Box-folder 1/68, 4/57, 4/73, 5/57, 7/8, 7/36-40, 10/30)
    - Adult Education for Homeless Annual Report [Reporte Anual sobre Educación para Personas sin Hogar], 1995 (Box-folder 4/57)
    - Adult Education for Homeless Annual Report [Reporte Anual sobre Educación para Adultos Sin Hogar], 1995 (Box-folder 5/57)
    - Annual Report [Reporte Anual] (Box-folder 4/73)
    - Annual Reports [Reportes Anuales], 2000-2002 (Box-folder 10/30)
    - CASA Latina Annual Report [Reportes Anuales de CASA Latina], 2001-2003 (Box-folder 1/68)
    - Annual Report [Reporte Anual], 2000 (Box-folder 7/36)
    - Annual Report [Reporte Anual], 2001 (Box-folder 7/37)
    - Annual Report [Reporte Anual], 2002 (Box-folder 7/38)
    - Annual Report [Reporte Anual], 2003 (Box-folder 7/39)
    - Annual Report [Reporte Anual], 2004 (Box-folder 7/40)
    - Annual Report [Reporte Anual], 2005 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Program and Outcomes Data [Subserie C: Datos sobre Programas y Resultados], 1996-2009; Subseries C (Box-folder 3/52, 3/80, 4/33, 8/39-40, 8/56-58, 10/21, 12/11, 13/7)
    - CASA Latina Data [Datos CASA Latina], 1996-1999 (Box-folder 4/33)
    - CASA Latina Data [Datos de CASA Latina], 2005 (Box-folder 3/52)
    - CASA Latina Comparative Table [Tabla Comparativa de CASA Latina], 2007-2008 (Box-folder 3/80)
    - Articles on Day Labor [Artículos sobre Trabajo a Jornal], 2000-2004 (Box-folder 8/39)
    - Data on Day Laborers [Datos sobre Jornaleros], 1999-2001 (Box-folder 8/40)
    - Workers who Obtained Permanent Employment [Trabajadores quienes Obtuvieron Empleo Permanente], 2006-2009 (Box-folder 8/58)
    - Data: Wage Claims, Workers' Center, ESL, Women's Group--Part 1 of 2 [Datos: Reclamos Salariales, Centro de Trabajadores, Clases de Inglés, Grupo de Mujeres--Parte 1 de 2], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Data: Wage Claims, Workers' Center, ESL, Women's Group--Part 2 of 2 [Datos: Reclamos Salariales, Centro de Trabajadores, Clases de Inglés, Grupo de Mujeres--Parte 2 de 2], 2004/2005 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Homeless Statistics [Estadística de Personas sin Hogar], 1996-2002 (Box-folder 8/56)
    - Poverty [Pobreza], 2001-2007 (Box-folder 8/57)
    - Hispanics--Data [Hispanos--Datos] (Box-folder 10/21)
- GENERAL OFFICE FILES [SERIE 4: ARCHIVOS GENERALES DE OFICINA], 1994-2009; SERIES 4 (Box-folder 1/39, 1/41, 3/5, 3/40, 3/42, 3/79, 3/81, 4/15, 4/39, 4/42, 4/51-53, 4/55-56, 4/69, 5/8, 5/21, 6/36, 7/3, 7/10-14, 7/16-35, 8/6, 8/8, 8/27, 9/11, 9/32, 9/38, 10/6)
  General correspondence, budgets and other financial records, capital campaign materials, strategic fundraising plans, and staff meeting materials. Related financial agreements may also be found in SERIES 6: CONTRACTS AND AGREEMENTS.[Correspondencia general, registros financieros, materiales de campaña de capital, planes de recaudación de fondos, y notas de reuniones de personal. Materiales relacionados a acuerdos financieros se encuentran en SERIE 6: CONTRATOS Y ACUERDOS.]
  - Correspondence [Subserie A: Correspondencia], 1999-2007; Subseries A (Box-folder 4/42, 6/36)
    - MISC. Correspondence [Correspondencia Misceláneo], 1999 (Box-folder 4/42)
    - 2007 Letters & Postcards, "A Brief History" CASA Latina comic book, and group photograph of unidentified individuals at CASA Latina [?] [Letras, Tarjetas Postales, y Revista de CASA Latina 2007] (Box-folder 6/36)
  - Financial Records [Subserie B: Registros Financieros], 1994-2009; Subseries B (Box-folder 1/39, 1/41, 3/40, 3/42, 3/79, 3/81, 4/15, 4/39, 4/69, 5/8, 5/21, 7/3, 7/10-14, 7/16-35, 8/6, 8/8, 8/27, 9/32, 9/38, 10/6)
    - Funding History [Historia del Financiamento], 1994-2004 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Budget of CASA Latina [Propuesto de CASA Latina], 1999 (Box-folder 4/39)
    - CASA Latina Workers' Budget [Presupuesto de Trabajadores CASA Latina], 1999 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - Funding & Accounting Calendar [Calendario de Fondos y Contabilidad], 2010 (Box-folder 1/41)
    - CASA Latina Profit & Loss Budget vs. Actual by Job [Propuesto de Pérdidas y Ganancias vs. Actual por Trabajo de CASA Latina], 2004 January-2004 August (Box-folder 3/40)
    - CASA Latina Profit & Loss Budget vs. Actual by Job [Propuesto de Pérdidas y Ganancias vs. Actual por Trabajo de CASA Latina], 2004 August-2005 January (Box-folder 3/42)
    - CASA Latina Proposed Budget [Propuesto de CASA Latina], 2009 (Box-folder 3/79)
    - CASA Latina Finance General [Finanza General CASA Latina], 2009-2010 (Box-folder 3/81)
    - CASA Latina Report on Review of Financial Statements [Reporte de Revisión de Estados Financieros CASA Latina], 1996 December (Box-folder 4/69)
    - CASA Latina Strategic Fundraising Plan [Plan para Recaudación de Fondos Estratégica], 2005-2009 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Strategic Fundraising Plan [Plan Estratégico para Recaudar Fondos], 2000-2009 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - City Audit Requirements (Seattle) [Requisitos de Auditoría por Ciudad (Seattle)], 1996-1999 (Box-folder 1/39)
    - Audit Report (Willett, Zevenbergen, & Bennett) [Informe de Auditoría (Willett, Zevenbergen, & Bennett)], 1997 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Audit Report (Willett, Zevenbergen, & Bennett) [Informe de Auditoría (Willett, Zevenbergen, & Bennett)], 1998 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - Audit Report & Contract (Willett, Zevenbergen, & Bennett) [Informe de Auditoría y Contrato (Willett, Zevenbergen, & Bennett)], 1998 (Box-folder 7/18)
    - Audit Letter & Contract (Willett, Zevenbergen, & Bennett) [Informe de Auditoría y Contrato (Willett, Zevenbergen, & Bennett)], 1999 (Box-folder 7/21)
    - Audit Letter & Contract (Messenger Finance Corporation) [Carta de Auditoría y Contrato (Corporación Financiera Messenger)], 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7/23)
    - Audit Letter & Contract (Messenger Finance Corporation) [Carta de Auditoría y Contrato (Corporación Financiera Messenger)], 2002 (Box-folder 7/24)
    - Audit Letter & Contract (Messenger Finance Corporation) [Carta de Auditoría y Contrato (Corporación Financiera Messenger)], 2003 (Box-folder 7/25)
    - Audit Letter & Contract (Messenger Finance Corporation) [Carta de Auditoría y Contrato (Corporación Financiera Messenger)], 2004 (Box-folder 7/26)
    - Audit Letter & Contract (Messenger Finance Corporation) [Carta de Auditoría y Contrato (Corporación Financiera Messenger)], 2005 (Box-folder 7/27)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax [Regreso a Organización Exento de Impuesto Sobre Ganancias], 1997 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax [Regreso a Organización Exento de Impuesto Sobre Ganancias], 1996 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax [Regreso a Organización Exento de Impuesto Sobre Ganancias], 1998 (Box-folder 7/19)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax [Regreso a Organización Exento de Impuesto Sobre Ganancias], 1999 (Box-folder 7/29)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax [Regreso a Organización Exento de Impuesto Sobre Ganancias], 2000 (Box-folder 7/30)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax [Regreso a Organización Exento de Impuesto Sobre Ganancias], 2001 (Box-folder 7/31)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax [Regreso a Organización Exento de Impuesto Sobre Ganancias], 2002 (Box-folder 7/32)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax [Regreso a Organización Exento de Impuesto Sobre Ganancias], 2003 (Box-folder 7/33)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax [Regreso a Organización Exento de Impuesto Sobre Ganancias], 2004 (Box-folder 7/34)
    - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax [Regreso a Organización Exento de Impuesto Sobre Ganancias], 2005 (Box-folder 7/35)
    - Report on Review of Financial Statements [Informe de Revisión de Estados Financieros], 1996 December 31 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Report on Examination of Financial Statements [Informe sobre Examen de Estados Financieros], 1997 December 31-1998 December 31 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Report on Examination of Financial Statements [Informe sobre Examen de Estados Financieros], 1998 December 31-1999 December 31 (Box-folder 7/20)
    - Report on Examination of Financial Statements [Informe sobre Examen de Estados Financieros], 1999 December 31-2000 December 31 (Box-folder 7/22)
    - Capital Campaign Feasibility Study Materials (Joan Caine) [Materiales del Estudio de Factibilidad de Campaña Capital (Joan Caine)], 2005 (Box-folder 8/27)
    - Capital Campaign [Campaña Capital], 2005 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - Capital Campaign [Campaña Capital], 2007 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Capital Campaign [Campaña Capital], 2009 (Box-folder 9/32)
    - County Council Budget Request [Solicitud de Presupuesto al Consejo del Condado], 2007 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - Letter of Certified public Accountant [Letra de Contador Público Certificado], 1996 (Box-folder 7/28)
    - TIAA-CREF Material [Materiales TIAA-CREF], 1997 (Box-folder 9/38)
  - Staff Meetings [Subserie C: Notas de la Reunión de Personal], 1994-2002; Subseries C (Box-folder 3/5, 4/51-53, 4/55-56, 9/11)
    - Meeting Notes of CASA Latina [Notas de la Reunión de CASA Latina], 2002 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - CASA Latina Staff Meeting Archive (1 of 3) [Archivo de Reuniones de Juntas de Empleados CASA Latina (1 de 3)], 1996-1997 (Box-folder 4/51)
    - CASA Latina Staff Meeting Archive (2 of 3) [Archivo de Reuniones de Juntas de Empleados CASA Latina (2 de 3)], 1996-1997 (Box-folder 4/52)
    - CASA Latina Staff Meeting Archive (3 of 3) [Archivo de Reuniones de Juntas de Empleados CASA Latina (3 de 3)], 1997 (Box-folder 4/53)
    - CASA Latina City Stuff Meeting (1 of 2), 1996 (Box-folder 4/55)
    - CASA Latina City Stuff Meeting (2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box-folder 4/56)
    - Staff Meetings [Juntas de Personal], 1994-1995 (Box-folder 9/11)
- PROGRAM FILES [SERIE 5: ARCHIVOS DE PROGRAMAS], 1992-2014; SERIES 5 (Box-folder 1/8, 1/11, 1/14, 1/21, 1/62-65, 1/86, 2/39-61, 2/76-77, 4/3, 4/18, 4/58, 5/2-6, 5/18, 5/9, 5/11, 5/13-14, 5/51, 6/1-21, 7/49, 7/50-52, 8/11-13, 8/17, 8/22, 8/28-32, 8/42-45, 8/52-55, 98-10, 9/12-15, 9/20-25, 9/33, 9/40, 9/42-43, 9/45, 9/47, 9/49, 9/50, 9/54, 10/4, 10/13-14, 10/22-29, 10/38-39, 11/3-10, 11/36, 11/46-55, 12/1-4, 13/2-3)
  Program planning, curricula, evaluations, summaries, and lobbying guides and research, (including the Underground Economy Task Force), for CASA Latina education and literacy programs, ESL classes and worker education workshops. [Planes para programas, currículo, evaluaciones, sumarios, y guías de cabildeo e investigación (incluyendo el proyecto Fuerza Especial de Economía Clandestina) para programas de educación y literacia, clases de inglés, y talleres para trabajadores.]
  - Education and Literacy Programs [Subserie A: Programas de Educación y Literacia], 1992-2008; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/14, 1/86, 4/18, 4/58, 5/2-4, 5/18, 5/9, 5/13-14, 7/49, 7/51-52, 8/52-53, 9/13, 9/25, 9/43, 9/45, 9/47, 9/49)
    - CASA Latina Student Enrollment Policy [Póliza de Inscripción de Estudiantes CASA Latina], 1995 September 9-1995 October 23 (Box-folder 4/58)
    - Seattle University Mentor Program [Programa de Mentores de Universidad de Seattle], 2008 (Box-folder 9/25)